HANNAH MACBRYDE

INDUSTRY SKILLS

HTML5 • CSS • JavaScript • jQuery

- React Tailwind SASS LESS
- Gulp BootStrap Adobe CC
- Figma Magento Storybook
- GIT
- UX/UI Wireframes SEO •Test Performance •

EDUCATION

BsC Creative Media Technology Leeds Beckett University Leeds, UK Sept 2013 - May 2016

BTEC Interactive Media Priestley College Warrington, UK Sept 2009 - July 2011

GCSE'S (Inc Maths & English) Great Sankey High School Warrington, UK Sept 2004 - July 2009

STRENGTHS

- Collaborative
- ✓ Detail-oriented
- () Time management
- **Adaptability**

UX Developer at PrettyLittleThing

📞 07710888045 🔞 hannahmacbryde@hotmail.co.uk 👑 20.08.1993

SUMMARY

UX professional with over 8 years of experience in UX development and front-end development, expert in A/B testing and user interface optimization. Key achievements include leading the development of over 500 A/B tests and elevating annual revenue by more than £24 million at PrettyLittleThing within a three year period, as well as increasing conversion rates by 80% through design improvements at PrettyLittleThing. Leveraging a tech stack that includes JavaScript, React, Tailwind CSS, and Git to build responsive, user-friendly web applications and ensure efficient version control.

EXPERIENCE

UX Developer

PrettyLittleThing

2022 - Present Manchester, UK

My role in the UX Department involved:

- Served as the sole full-time developer on the UX team, leading the development of 500+ A/B tests and 100% experiences, driving an annual revenue increase of over £24 million across a three-year period through WebTrends Optimize.
- Partnered with the UX designers during weekly calls to provide feedback and improvement decisions on designs and deciding on the overall build capabilities through WebTrends integration.
- Consistently exceeded capacity expectations by operating at 113%, fostering strong collaboration with designers, analysts, and product owners to accelerate A/B builds.

Front End Developer

PrettyLittleThing

2018 - 2022 Manchester, UK

My role in the Studio Department involved:

- Developed CMS pages and campaign mock-ups with a focus on maintaining high quality standards and maximizing customer satisfaction.
- Mentored fellow developers through regular code reviews and provided support in resolving blockers, ensuring smooth project workflow and maintaining high standards.
- Assisted the graphic designers with development feedback on campaign wireframes and mockups. Leading their designs to reach full potential with enhanced jQuery performances.

Junior Front End Developer

PrettyLittleThing

2016 - 2018 Manchester, UK

My role in the Studio Department involved:

- •Assisted in the fast turn arounds of campaign pages from mockups to live site. These turn arounds could be as fast as within 1 day to build.
- •Improved my knowledge of tech stack to a higher standard and implemented CMS updates through Magento using a Bootstrap framework.